[{
	"Question": "How many of these lightposts are at the main gate?",
	"answerA": "6",
	"answerB": "8",
	"answerC": "10",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "How many silver poles are around the clock?",
	"answerA": "16",
	"answerB": "18",
	"answerC": "20",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "What is the other girl like this holding?",
	"answerA": "Bird",
	"answerB": "Umbrella",
	"answerC": "Flower",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What year did the City of Brisbane buy the land for New Farm Park?",
	"answerA": "1893",
	"answerB": "1913",
	"answerC": "1937",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "How many harps are in the bandstand?",
	"answerA": "4",
	"answerB": "6",
	"answerC": "8",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "How many steps down to the river?",
	"answerA": "13",
	"answerB": "15",
	"answerC": "17",
	"answerD": "19,
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What year's flood does this marker commemorate?",
	"answerA": "1893",
	"answerB": "1974",
	"answerC": "2010",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{
	"Question": "What is the artwork called?",
	"answerA": "Flood",
	"answerB": "Rising Water",
	"answerC": "Watermark",
	"answerD": "High Tide",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "Eat, drink and be ...",
	"answerA": "Mary",
	"answerB": "Merry",
	"answerC": "Married",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "What fruit can you find in this mural?",
	"answerA": "Apple",
	"answerB": "Banana",
	"answerC": "Orange",
	"answerD": "Strawberry",
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "Who have you been reported to?",
	"answerA": "The Police",
	"answerB": "The Premier",
	"answerC": "The Authorities",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "Cs"
},
{	"Question": "What does the sign say?",
	"answerA": "Start",
	"answerB": "Go",
	"answerC": "Stop",
	"answerD": "Hammer time",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "Who is the artist?",
	"answerA": "Mark Scottes",
	"answerB": "Scott Marsh",
	"answerC": "Max Galves",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{
	"Question": "What year was the Powerhouse Centre for the Arts opened?",
	"answerA": "1988",
	"answerB": "1999",
	"answerC": "2000",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "Where does the bikeway go to?",
	"answerA": "Fortitude Valley",
	"answerB": "Kangaroo Point",
	"answerC": "Newstead",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "How many dragon eggs have completely hatched?",
	"answerA": "2",
	"answerB": "3",
	"answerC": "4",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "What amphibian can you find here?",
	"answerA": "Crocodile",
	"answerB": "Frog",
	"answerC": "Turtle",
	"answerD": "Snake",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "What mythical creatures surround this tree?",
	"answerA": "fairies",
	"answerB": "Dragons",
	"answerC": "Unicorns",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "What mythical creature can you see through this window?",
	"answerA": "Fairy",
	"answerB": "Dragon",
	"answerC": "Unicorn",
	"answerD":
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What season is located North East?",
	"answerA": "Autumn",
	"answerB": "Winter",
	"answerC": "Spring",
	"answerD": "Summer",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
}
]